PREVIOUSLY
Hey, it's me, Uncle.
[Jinwoo] Miss Jeong Jian?
Uh, Mr. Jeong Jinman has been found dead.
[Jian] This is what my uncle sold?
You being serious?
THEN… IS JEONG JINMAN DEAD?
THEN… YOU'LL DIE TODAY TOO,
JEONG JIAN?
[thudding sound]
[inhales sharply]
[gasps]
[screams, grunts]
[Seongjo] Wow!
The veteran warriors
have all gathered together!
[shatters]
The first person who manages
to kill Jinman's niece
or captures her alive
will bring home a big fat bonus.
All right, the rabbit hunt begins!
[thuds, whirs]
[whirring]
[Jinman] Listen up, Jeong Jian.
Whatever scares you,
keep your eyes open and face it head-on.
[Minhye] I see that you don't think
before you act.
That's not what your uncle would do.
Yes, on the floor
where your uncle did most of his work
is a door that opens into Murthehelp.
-No way.
-[thuds]
[Jeongmin] It actually exists.
[high-pitched ringing]
Wait, no, please, it's too bright.
You haven't answered my question yet!
[Brother] Jeong Jian!
D-d-don't trust him!
[gasps]
Jeongmin!
[♪ tense music playing]
[Seongjo] But there is something
you should know.
Your Uncle Jinman killed
a lot of people too.
[Bale] You and I both get paid
to kill people.
Stop pretending to be righteous.
It makes me sick.
In the end, you and I
are more alike than you think.
[both grunting]
[Bale] If you don't kill me here,
I'll kill everyone.
All your friends, and family, and anyone
who has anything to do with you.
-[gasps]
-[Kuma] You must be Jeong Jian.
-You really do take after your uncle.
-[heavy breathing]
[Jian] That you, Master?
[Pasin] We don't have time, Jian.
Bale's after you.
[Bale] You're up, you two.
Go and handle this.
[engine revving]
[crashes]
[♪ tense music playing]
Hey there, twins.
Today is the day we go to Hell.
[fighting grunts]
[grunts]
Jian, you better run!
-Minhye!
-Get outta here!
[cries]
[Jinman] I'll give you two options
to choose from.
But ultimately,
the choice is yours to make.
-[Jian screams]
-[gunshots]
[Seongjo exclaiming]
[gunshot]
[♪ tense music playing]
[inhales]
[screaming]
[Bale] It should be me…
[♪ soft tense music playing]
who takes his life away.
Don't you think?
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
[footsteps thudding]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[staff 1] Team Leader?
[alarm wailing]
What's going on?
[grunts, groans]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[staff 2] It's the server room! Move, now!
[alarm wailing continues]
STYLE
::cue()
[clicks]
[sighs]
[warped droning intensifies]
[explosion]
[♪ muffled suspenseful music playing]
[high-pitched ringing]
[♪ tense music intensifies]
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 01
JINMAN ON THE SAME DAY
[♪ pensive music playing]
[Jeongmin] Wait! Jeong Jinman!
You have to let me down!
Hey, you fucker!
[door opens]
[Jeongmin laughing]
[laughing continues]
-[machines thudding]
-[alarm beeping]
[cell phone buzzing]
[Jinwoo] Time of death is 1900 hours.
I've transferred the body
to the Hansarang Gyeongae Hospital
mortuary in Yecheong County.
His niece Jeong Jian
is his only surviving family.
No need to involve Yecheong Police.
[keys jingling]
[lock clanking]
[beeping]
[lock clicks open]
[♪ soft music playing]
[clicking]
[Jinwoo] North Korean defector.
Can't believe you're still alive.
Well, that's because security
in South Korea's
-become soft since I've been gone.
-[chuckles]
Look at you.
You don't look like
you've come across any guards.
-Hey.
-[chuckles]
[laughs]
Officer Jinwoo.
Pasin.
-[speaking Thai] Jinwoo-krap.
-[in English] How are you?
You're working out too much.
Yeah, well, for a cop,
you're a skinny little bitch.
[chuckles]
[door slides open]
Starting now, we have 62 hours.
Babylon…
took our bait.
STYLE
::cue()
[associate] From the outside,
this place looks exactly like
every other run-of-the-mill rice factory.
One of the buildings even operates
as a rice warehouse.
But it's just a cover.
A full one-kilometer radius spanning
all directions is completely flat land.
Anyone approaching
will be spotted immediately.
This place is a fortress.
[whooshing]
[whirs]
[alarm wailing]
The assholes have upgraded.
Now we have to get around all of that.
[sighs]
[associate] Most of Babylon's facilities
are installed on their basement floors.
The armory is on basement four.
The situation room, basement two.
There's a 30-millimeter AA gun
on the rooftop.
[associate] Ninety-six soldiers
of Babylon's mobile force
are active until 6:00 p.m.
But, Jinman, it's supposed
to be a surprise, isn't it?
It would be better
to kill Bale somewhere else.
[Jinman] This is the target.
[burbling]
[Pasin] The server?
[Jinman] It houses all
of Babylon's classified files.
They've been around
since the military dictatorship.
Babylon's carried out
all the intelligence operations,
kidnappings, and assassinations
on behalf of every changing regime.
Including selling North Korea weapons
behind our government's back.
In the conflict zones
of Southeast and Central Asia,
they made arms deals
with both rebels and government forces.
Political coups were engineered
for their own gain.
Decades of client lists,
intelligence operatives,
all their contract kill data.
Everything top secret
is being kept in there.
Bale killed hundreds of civilians
during operations.
That evidence is buried there as well.
This is our bargaining chip.
Babylon will have no choice
but to be kept in check.
The result is a maintained
state of neutrality.
If our plan fails…
this exhausting,
useless war will never end for us.
Jian deserves to live a full
and peaceful life.
[Jinman] We can't fail.
Jian needs us to protect her
with this shield.
[Jinwoo] Can't we just hack the data?
Impossible. [clicks tongue]
In order to keep it secure
and to prevent overheating,
they keep it separate
from the general server room
and store it independently underwater.
This wall is made of concrete
and serves as the firewall.
[sighs]
Even so, it has to be connected
to somewhere outside, right?
True, but it's still submerged underwater.
[sighs]
Ah, even a Kim Il Sung University elite
is stumped, huh? [clicks tongue]
Collect the reward and report the spy.
This asshole's useless.
What do you propose instead?
We're removing the whole thing.
[associate] At 1500 hours every day,
the server is raised
from the water tank for inspection.
[Pasin] Great. We'll hack it then.
What the hell, how'd this Thai idiot
ever work with Babylon?
You should keep your dumb mouth shut.
[clicks tongue]
Watch your step, man.
[water trickling]
[machine whirring, beeping]
[heavy thud]
[♪ tense music playing]
[associate] This is our chance.
But we'll only have 20 minutes.
Infiltrating the enemy network
and downloading the data that quickly?
It's impossible even for Zuckerberg.
Zuck, who… who is that?
Just say hacking, come on.
Thai genius.
You're gonna have to be the one
that brings the new-model bomb
to my location.
Oh, yeah?
Why is that?
Because you're good.
[Jinman] We can't take weapons
inside Babylon,
so we'll go through the armory.
Team leaders and up
can carry personal sidearms,
but they're only allowed
to access the ammo
during an active operation.
[smacks lips]
The armory has what we need.
We'll have to raid it for weapons.
[Jinman] In the explosive section,
you'll find the E5 bombs,
which were specially manufactured
as miniature bunker-busters.
With those, we'll blast into the rooms
above and below the server.
I take the bombs
and blast it into the server?
Pasin, you also have to plant a bomb
above the server on the first floor.
STYLE
::cue()
That'll be really tough.
Why can't you stop complaining?
I have it just as bad.
Look over there.
It's not always about the big things.
The most physical things
aren't always the toughest.
My issue…
is figuring out what bait
will reel this guy in.
[sighs]
BEAUTIFUL FEMALE MASSEUSE!!
ALWAYS ON STANDBY!!
PREMIUM-QUALITY MASSAGE
GRAND OPENING SPECIAL!
[sighs]
DELETE MESSAGES
[door opens, closes]
DELETE ALL
[scoffs]
To defeat your enemies,
you must think like your enemies.
[crickets chirping]
[keyboard clacking]
[beeping]
THE PROFESSOR HAS SELECTED
TOMORROW'S SURGE STOCK.
South Koreans and capitalism.
Gets them every time.
[beeping]
KIM JUNGHO
SECURITY TEAM LEADER
[whirring]
That's cool.
KIM JUNGHO
SECURITY TEAM LEADER
[Jinman] Most of Babylon's waste
is handled
at its own incineration facility.
But a designated company collects
the regular trash once a week.
This is the only opening we have
to infiltrate, so we need to be ready.
[creaking]
[spray hissing]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
WASTE COLLECTION
& TRANSPORT SPECIALISTS 1643-8834
[crinkling]
92 MEO 0583
[creaking]
[soft groan]
[grunts]
Mm-hmm.
You're trash.
Thai garbage.
We're trash together.
[crinkling]
PARANG ENVIRONMENT
WASTE COLLECTION & TRANSPORT
SPECIALISTS 1643-8834
Once we get through the entrance…
we still have to pass the X-ray.
STOP
[alarm buzzing]
[associate] I'm gonna wrap
a layer of X-ray resistant film
inside the trash bins.
It's the same expensive film
the Americans use
in their stealth aircrafts.
That's right.
Cheolseung here
will hack into Babylon's intranet for us.
[Jinman] He'll secure the CCTVs
located on our route.
Pasin and I will go to the armory
and grab the bombs and the weapons
that we'll need.
Pasin will plant the E5 on the first floor
and move to the server room.
That leaves Bale.
Bale is mine.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[trilling]
[whirring]
[Cheolseung] Everything about
the replica is perfect.
Except there's nothing I can do
about his left eye.
You'll have to put on dark sunglasses
or something to hide it.
[buzzing]
JEONG JIAN
[cell phone buzzing continues]
[cell phone vibrating]
[Jian] Hey, it's me, Uncle.
Miss Jeong Jian?
[Jian] Who is this?
This is Sergeant Park Jinwoo
from the Yecheong Police Station.
I was actually just about to call you.
[Jian] Oh.
And why is that?
[Jinwoo] Well, I'm sorry
to have to tell you this.
Uh, Mr. Jeong Jinman has been found dead.
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ wistful music playing]
Miss Jeong Jian?
Ah.
I'm Sergeant Park Jinwoo.
DETECTIVE DIVISION / VIOLENT CRIMES TEAM
2 PARK JINWOO
Right.
If you're ready.
[door opens]
[♪ wistful music continues]
[Jinwoo] She looked like she was in shock.
But she accepted it.
Okay.
Good work, Jinwoo.
We'll be waiting for you.
[Pasin] Keep going. Straight ahead.
How many minutes will it take?
About 47.
No. See if you can make it 40.
[Cheolseung] Copy.
-[sighs]
-[loud thud]
-[heavy clank]
-[alarm beeping]
Did Jian buy it?
My funeral's in 48 hours.
It's also when we're mobilizing.
Those Code Reds…
are they trustworthy?
Like human nature,
wolves follow their pack leader.
We'll put our trust in Mr. Kim.
[ship horn honking]
[Yonghan] I'm sorry, Mr. Kim.
It's my fault.
I should've taken better care of things.
Well, that's how life is sometimes.
I didn't blame you,
not even once, Yonghan.
But you're asking me
to betray Jinman, posthumously.
Is that right?
Seongjo's proposal… [sighs]
You turned him down.
I should have come to see you myself.
I'm sorry.
[thudding]
A document?
It's a contract.
It's my olive branch.
I want you to come work with us.
Supervise our training center.
You'll be able to restore
your damaged reputation.
You'll be able to live comfortably
from now on.
[♪ tense music playing]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[car alarm beeps]
MR. KIM
HAS STEPPED OUTSIDE THE FENCE.
[engine rumbling]
[Jinman] Pasin and Cheolseung
will infiltrate first.
WASTE COLLECTION &
TRANSPORT SPECIALISTS 1643-8834
STYLE
::cue()
External vehicles will be directed
to the underground loading dock.
[alarm buzzing]
[alarm buzzing continues]
STOP
First time here?
Oh, yeah, Seunghoon
was supposed to be on today.
But he's out with COVID.
I'm just filling in while he's sick.
WASTE COLLECTION 13:30
LEE SEUNGHOON
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[guard] Look.
[dog panting]
Get out.
What?
[engine shuts off]
Um, uh… Is something the matter here or?
The back.
[soft grunt]
[sighs]
[door lock clanking]
Open it.
[Jinwoo] Okay.
So…
Uh, the thing is…
This is really… [grunts]
[guard sighs in disgust]
Smelly stuff.
I stopped by the hospital this morning.
Argh, the smell of blood. Shit.
Do you want to open all of these?
No. No need for all that. You can shut it.
I know. [laughs]
It's gross.
I never get used to the smell either.
[alarm buzzing]
[alarm beeping]
[groans]
Help me out of here.
[sighs] Look at this Thai trashhole.
[grunting]
[footsteps thudding]
[gun clicking]
Jeong Jinman's dead, so what's the rush?
-Hey. Seongjo's pissed off, man, hurry up.
-[mercenary 1] No, I got it.
Should we buy something sweet on the way?
I don't think we should go empty-handed.
[mercenary 2] We're moving out!
[mercenary 3] Moving out, let's go!
[engine rumbling]
[tires squealing]
Shit.
[tires screeching]
[tires squealing]
Captain, the situation
just got complicated.
STYLE
::cue()
[groans, pants]
[groans]
[mumbles]
-[sighs]
-[cell phone buzzes]
[♪ tense music playing]
BROTHER THE SEAGULL IS INJURED,
THE EAGLET IS INSIDE IN THE SHOPPING MALL
[Pasin] Kuma's headed to the shopping mall
with his team.
[sighs]
Pasin, you and Jinwoo withdraw.
Cheolseung, stay put.
[clicks tongue]
Well, guess I'm staying here.
Ah, come on.
Just go.
Hey there, spy.
Don't you die.
[scoffs]
[♪ soft tense music playing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[soft thudding]
[doors close]
[sighs] Pasin,
head on over to Jian.
Minhye can't handle Kuma and his team
on her own, so give her a hand.
Jinman.
None of us are gonna be
going to Hell today.
Jian, she's got all of us to protect her.
[♪ soft tense music playing]
[pants, grunts]
[Jinwoo] Captain.
Cheolseung has reached his first position.
[sighs]
[whirring]
[grunts]
[soft click]
Ah, ah.
Bale.
You're going to Hell today.
[clicking]
[beeping]
STYLE
::cue()
[guard] What can I do about that?
[gulps, sighs]
You need to just be honest with him.
[Jinwoo] Bale and Yonghan are located
in the situation room.
Confirmed.
[Cheolseung] Hold on.
If Pasin left,
who's gonna bring me the bomb?
I'm headed over there right now.
[Jinman] Once I confirm I'm in,
move to your second position.
Copy.
DANGER SLOWLY
SEGEON RICE MILL
Team Leader, how've you been?
[trilling]
[clicking]
[beeps]
[guard] Wait a minute.
-Why?
-[guard sucks teeth]
[guard] That's Team Leader Three.
-And?
-He entered at 0900 hours.
He's back,
but there's no record of him leaving.
[sighs] This is such a hassle. Shit.
I'm sorry.
Let me just check one thing.
Call whoever was on duty this morning.
[keyboard clacking]
-[beeping]
-[line rings]
[line ringing continues]
Why isn't he picking up?
Damn idiot.
Yeah.
Hey, this is the main gate.
Where was Team Leader Three
this morning after about 0900?
Ah, he was… at the firing range
at 1200, I believe.
Got it. Here.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[chuckles]
Which firing range did you go to today?
Forget it.
Open the gate.
I'll proceed
with the password verification.
Hey, he's already been through today.
I'm sorry about this. Truly.
Uh, it's protocol, so I have to do it.
[guard] Phoenix.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Password, password, password.
[Cheolseung] What is it?
These Babylon assholes.
I've never done this before.
[♪ tense music playing]
What's the stupid password? Shit.
I told you to open it.
I'm just following the procedure here.
It's all right.
Rifle.
Are we good?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
CODE: PHOENIX / RIFFLE
[exasperated sigh]
That was tougher than clearing mines
on the demarcation line.
[sighs]
[inhales]
I'm moving to my next position.
STYLE
::cue()
[elevator bell dings]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[metallic clanking]
[metallic clanking continues]
[trilling]
[beeps]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Okay.
Cheolseung's moved
into his second position.
Standby.
[♪ upbeat music continues]
[Jinwoo] Ten minutes remaining.
Armory CCTVs?
[Cheolseung] They're no problem.
DANGER
I'm returning my gun.
[beeps]
[whirring]
EXPLOSIVE MATERIALS
WARNING EXPLOSIVE MATERIAL
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[beeps]
[alarm wails]
[clicks]
[whirring, rattling]
[whirring]
[trills, beeps]
[Jinwoo] It's almost time.
What's going on?
[whirring]
[machine beeping]
What is it?
Someone tell me what's going on.
[heavy thud]
[scraping]
[♪ tense music playing]
[grunts]
Now is your only chance.
[electric crackling]
[whirs]
[grunts]
[panting]
[door closes]
STYLE
::cue()
Uh, Chief?
I think we need to check
Team Leader Bale's location.
Why?
I walked past him in the situation room
a few minutes ago,
but then, two minutes later,
I ran into him on a different floor.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
[groans]
[panting]
Huh?
Team Leader Bale has two cars on site?
[♪ tense music playing]
[creaking]
[♪ tense music continues]
[Jinman grunts]
[strained grunt]
[sighs]
The inspection is complete.
[beeps]
[whirs]
I have to go down.
Something weird's going on.
Hey, wait a sec.
What are you going to do?
[door whirs open]
[machine beeping]
[both grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[loud thud]
[Cheolseung panting]
Ah, shit.
[panting]
[sighs]
I took care of the first floor.
I was waiting forever,
I thought you died in there.
[exhales]
Glad you're alive.
I won't die today.
[panting]
Or ever.
Check the route and radius of movement
to see where that vehicle came from,
and run a malware scan.
-We could've been hacked.
-Yes, sir.
[drones whirring]
[♪ intense music playing]
[whirs]
[beeping]
[groaning]
[Cheolseung]
Server room installation complete.
Okay.
Ah, shit.
My location's been compromised.
STYLE
::cue()
[staff] Team two has arrived.
Ten minutes to entry.
General.
Jeong Jinman…
Do you think he's still alive?
[door opens]
Sir, one of the drones has been shot,
and we've been hacked.
What? What's wrong?
[alarm wailing]
Oh, shit. That son of a bitch.
What's going on? Go find out.
[explosion]
[loud blast]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[♪ tense music playing]
-[high-pitched warbling]
-[all groaning in pain]
[groaning continues]
17 MEO 4396
[♪ tense music continues]
[beeping]
[explodes]
[hissing]
[Bale grunts]
[Jinman grunts]
[groans]
-[grunts]
-[Jinman groans]
[panting]
[Bale] When I heard you were dead,
I was so disappointed.
[♪ dark, ominous music playing]
What?
You're not scared?
[both grunting]
STYLE
::cue()
[fierce grunts]
[yells]
[both groan]
[♪ action music playing]
[fighting grunts]
-[Bale groans]
-[thuds]
[panting]
See you later.
[inaudible screaming]
[bomb timers beeping]
[beeping continues]
[explosion]
[muffled explosion]
[loud rumbling]
[pants]
[panting]
[Yonghan] Jinman!
It's over.
It's time to end this.
[drones whirring]
[gunfire]
[helicopter blades whirring]
Shoot him down, idiots!
[gunfire]
[♪ tense music playing]
[clatters]
[sighs]
[panting]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ somber music playing]
[driver] It's dangerous out here.
You should go back inside
and wait in the shopping mall.
Sir. Someone is heading
this way right now.
You just stay here.
It's all right.
[bird squawking]
[driver] Are they one of ours?
No, sir, they haven't been confirmed.
[Jinwoo] Jinman, we're almost there.
[labored breathing]
[birds chirping]
I know that man.
[sighs]
[grunts]
[labored breathing]
[relieved sigh]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[grunts, pants]
[furious grunting]
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
[♪ dark, ominous music playing]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[♪ electronic dance music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
SIGMA
[cell phone vibrating]
[vibrating continues]
-Yeah?
-[Jun] Onee-chan,
you're too old to be playing
around in clubs.
I'm not playing.
-I'm working.
-[Jun scoffs]
[Jun] How'd you get in?
Security must be slacking,
they let anyone in these days.
You've got to be joking.
I can get in wherever I want.
[Jun laughing] Yeah, you wish.
I'm working, stop interfering.
What is it that you want?
[Jun] The director is summoning you.
What, why?
-[sighs]
-[Jun] Jeong Jinman.
Do you remember him?
I remember.
[♪ closing theme music playing]